<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site. -->
<!-- It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content. -->
<!-- You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another. -->
<!-- This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site. -->

<!-- To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps: -->
<!-- 1. Log in to that site as an administrator. -->
<!-- 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel. -->
<!-- 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list. -->
<!-- 4. Activate & Run Importer. -->
<!-- 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page. -->
<!-- 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users -->
<!--    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an -->
<!--    existing user on the site or to create a new user. -->
<!-- 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc. -->
<!--    contained in this file into your site. -->

<!-- generator="WordPress/4.4-alpha-34525" created="2015-09-24 22:21" -->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/"
>

<channel>
	<title>vip.local</title>
	<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com</link>
	<description>Just another Vip.local site</description>
	<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 22:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
	<wp:base_site_url>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/</wp:base_site_url>
	<wp:base_blog_url>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com</wp:base_blog_url>

	<wp:author><wp:author_id>1</wp:author_id><wp:author_login><![CDATA[wordpress]]></wp:author_login><wp:author_email><![CDATA[admin@example.com]]></wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[wordpress]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>


	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=4.4-alpha-34525</generator>

	<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2015/08/24/hello-world/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 21:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://vip.local/?p=1</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Welcome to <a href="http://vip.local/">Vip.local</a>. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>1</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2015-08-24 21:35:22]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2015-08-24 21:35:22]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[hello-world]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[trash]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_trash_meta_status]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_trash_meta_time]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1440533575]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_trash_meta_comments_status]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:1;s:1:"1";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:comment>
			<wp:comment_id>1</wp:comment_id>
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Mr WordPress]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url>http://vip.local/</wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_author_IP><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author_IP>
			<wp:comment_date><![CDATA[2015-08-24 21:35:22]]></wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt><![CDATA[2015-08-24 21:35:22]]></wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Hi, this is a comment.
To delete a comment, just log in and view the post&#039;s comments. There you will have the option to edit or delete them.]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved><![CDATA[post-trashed]]></wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
			<wp:comment_user_id>0</wp:comment_user_id>
		</wp:comment>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Internet.org: Myths and Facts</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2015/08/03/internet-org-myths-and-facts/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 15:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=6</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<strong>MYTH: Internet.org doesn’t help people connect to the internet.</strong>

<strong>FACT:</strong> Internet.org brings new people onto mobile networks on average over 50% faster after launching free basic services. This means that if 1,000 people who were brand new to the internet were signing up per month for mobile data services before launching Internet.org, 1,500 people sign up per month after launching Internet.org.

Through our connectivity efforts we’ve brought more than 9 million people online that otherwise would not be and introduced them to the incredible value of the internet. People now have access to basic internet services including tools and resources for communication, health, education and local news.

<strong>MYTH: Internet.org creates a two-tiered Internet.</strong>

<strong>FACT:</strong> Internet.org doesn’t create a two-tiered internet. It gives people an onramp to the internet, and after using free basic services, they understand the value of the internet and then access the internet outside of Internet.org. 50% of people who join Internet.org are paying for data – and therefore have decided to access the internet outside of free basic services – within 30 days of coming online for the first time. Not having programs like Internet.org leaves more people offline and unable to realize the benefits of the internet.

<strong>MYTH: Internet.org is an exclusive program available to only one operator per country.</strong>

<strong>FACT:</strong> Internet.org is non-exclusive and is open to any operator who wants to participate. In Malawi and the Philippines, Internet.org launched with multiple operators.

<strong>MYTH: Facebook pays operators to zero rate the services within Internet.org.</strong>

<strong>FACT:</strong> Facebook does not pay operators for the data that people consume. It partners with operators on the technical side and provides marketing support to help make people aware of the program. If successful, people using the internet for the first time will begin to experience its benefits and over time will start exploring and paying to use the broader internet.

<strong>MYTH: Facebook wants to keep people within a “walled garden” of free content.</strong>

<strong>FACT:</strong> Internet.org is successful only if the newly connected reach the broader internet. Operators can’t afford to invest in improving their infrastructure if new users never pay for data. Facebook launched the Internet.org Platform, which helps more developers to include their services in Internet.org and gives people greater choice over the services that they want to use. We also emphasize the importance of exploring the entire internet in our developer terms for the Internet.org Platform.

<strong>MYTH: Internet.org is a threat to local innovation.</strong>

<strong>FACT:</strong> There is no greater threat to local innovation than leaving people offline. Internet.org increases the potential audience for websites and services and helps bring more people online faster, using the entire internet. Facebook offers a broad package of tools for companies to help launch their service – both in and out of Internet.org, and holds developer events globally to connect with and help developers launch their online services.

<strong>MYTH: Many people think that Facebook is the entire internet, and Facebook is trying to use Internet.org to reinforce that impression.</strong>

<strong>FACT:</strong> Internet.org introduces people to the value of the internet through more than 100 free basic services globally. Giving people a list that features a broader set of services is important for helping people experience the value of other online services, like women’s health information and education services. Also a key guideline for developer participation in Internet.org is to encourage the exploration of the entire internet.

<strong>MYTH: Facebook has launched Internet.org to help drive its own growth and revenue opportunities within developing countries.</strong>

<strong>FACT:</strong> There are no ads within the Facebook experience on Internet.org. If revenue were the goal, Facebook would have focused resources on markets where online advertising is already thriving.

<strong>MYTH: Facebook is picking winners by independently selecting the services included in Internet.org.</strong>

<strong>FACT:</strong> Today, Internet.org offers more than 100 free basic services globally. Facebook recently announced the Internet.org Platform, which gives more developers an opportunity to include their services in Internet.org and gives people choice over the services that they want to use. A key guideline for developer participation is to encourage the exploration of the entire internet.

<strong>MYTH: Internet.org violates the principles of net neutrality.</strong>

<strong>FACT:</strong> Facebook supports net neutrality and has worked throughout the world to ensure that services can't be blocked or throttled and to ensure that fast lanes are prohibited. Net Neutrality seeks to ensure that network operators don’t limit access to services people want to use, and Internet.org's goal is to provide more people with access. It is good for consumer choice and consumer value. Net neutrality and Internet.org can and must co-exist.

<strong>MYTH: Internet.org does not provide adequate protections for new internet users, some of whom may not understand how their data will be used, or may not be able to properly give consent for certain practices.</strong>

<strong>FACT:</strong> Internet.org’s practices are clear, and Facebook and Internet.org take user privacy and security extremely seriously. Internet.org doesn't share user-level navigation information with any of its partners, and there is no requirement for developers participating in the Internet.org Platform to send Internet.org any information that personally identifies people. Internet.org does receive some data on navigation information because it needs to determine what traffic can be delivered free of data charges. This information is used, for example, to understand what services are popular, which helps it determine what types of services to launch in other countries. Internet.orgdoes not store this information with information that personally identifies you beyond 90 days.

<strong>MYTH: Isn't Facebook in this just to make money?</strong>

<strong>FACT:</strong> No company pays Facebook to be included in Internet.org. Facebook does not even show ads in Internet.org. If our partners run ads within their services, then people may see those ads just like the rest of the internet.

<strong>MYTH: Internet.org undermines user security and fails to implement HTTPS encryption. Internet.org will reject any site that uses SSL/TLS encryption, which makes user traffic vulnerable to malicious attacks and government eavesdropping.</strong>

FACT: Our goal is to provide a secure service on every supported platform and for everyone using Internet.org. To that end, we have rolled out HTTPS support for the Internet.org app and we are also investigating how we could provide similar security for web-based access to Internet.org.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Fast facts about Internet.org and free basic services.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>36</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2015-08-03 15:26:11]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2015-08-03 15:26:11]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[internet-org-myths-and-facts]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_excerpt_image]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_thumbnail_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[146]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>One Year In: Internet.org Free Basic Services</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2015/07/27/one-year-in-internet-org-free-basic-services/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 15:36:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=9</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[This week marks the one-year anniversary of the introduction of the Internet.org app in its first country, Zambia.



Over the past 12 months we’ve worked closely with more than a dozen mobile operators across 17 countries to give people access to relevant basic internet services without data charges, and today Internet.org is available to more than a billion people.



By providing people with access to free basic services through Internet.org, our goal was to bring more people online and help them discover the value of the internet — and it’s working.



Internet.org brings new users onto mobile networks on average over 50% faster after launching free basic services, and more than half of the people who come online through Internet.org are paying for data and accessing the internet within the first 30 days. These points show that Internet.org is not only a successful tool in helping bring people online, but it is successful in showing people the value of the internet and helping to accelerate its adoption.



As we approach year two, we’ve taken everything we’ve learned from working closely with our partners and are now ready to scale Internet.org free basic services. We’ve made it easier for any mobile operator to turn on Internet.org in new countries through a partner portal that includes technical tools and best practices, improving the process to offer free basic services to the unconnected. New operator partners can get started at <a href="https://internet.org/operators">internet.org/operators</a>.



With our recently announced Internet.org Platform, we've also made it easy for any developer to create services that integrate with Internet.org. Our goal is to work with as many mobile operators and developers as possible to extend the benefits of connectivity to diverse, local communities around the world.



In the past month people using Internet.org accessed health services more than a million times, which speaks to the ultimate goal of Internet.org — helping to make an impact in people's lives.



We look forward to working in partnership with more mobile operators and developers to bring internet access and relevant basic internet services to the unconnected.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Over the past 12 months we’ve worked closely with more than a dozen mobile operators across 17 countries to give people access to relevant basic internet services without data charges, and today Internet.org is available to more than a billion people.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>37</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2015-07-27 15:36:06]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2015-07-27 15:36:06]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[one-year-in-internet-org-free-basic-services]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Announcing the Internet.org Platform</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2015/05/04/announcing-the-internet-org-platform/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 15:44:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=11</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[[io_video id="204"]

Today, we’re introducing the Internet.org Platform, an open program for developers to easily create services that integrate with Internet.org. We’re also giving people more choice over the free basic services they can use.

Our goal with Internet.org is to work with as many developers and entrepreneurs as possible to extend the benefits of connectivity to diverse, local communities. To do this, we’re going to offer services through Internet.org in a way that’s more transparent and inclusive.

<strong>Our approach</strong>

At the core of our efforts with Internet.org are non-exclusive partnerships with mobile operators to offer free basic internet services to people through Internet.org. This is a set of basic websites and services to introduce people to the value of the internet, and that we hope add value to their lives.

These websites are very simple and data efficient, so operators can offer these for free in an economically sustainable way. Websites do not pay to be included, and operators don’t charge developers for the data people use for their services.

Because these services have to be specially built to these specifications, we started by offering just a few. But giving people more choice over the services they use is incredibly important and going forward, people using Internet.org will be able to search for and use services that meet these guidelines.

We're building an open platform and anyone who meets these guidelines will be able to participate.

Developers that join will need to follow three principles that we’ve followed in building versions of Facebook and Messenger for Internet.org. These are designed to align all participants’ incentives and bring more people online. Participation will remain free for any developer or user.

We think these criteria will help us to connect more people faster, and add even greater value to people’s lives.

<strong>Guidelines for participation</strong>

<strong>1. Explore the entire internet</strong>

The goal of Internet.org is to allow more people to experience the benefits of being online.

For most people who aren’t online, the biggest barrier to connecting isn’t lack of infrastructure - more than 80% of the world’s population already lives within range of a mobile signal. Instead, the biggest challenges are affordability of the internet, and awareness of how internet services are valuable to them.

The Internet.org Platform aims to give people valuable free services that they can use to discover the entire wealth of online services and, ultimately become paying users of the internet.

Services should encourage the exploration of the broader internet wherever possible.

<strong>2. Efficiency</strong>

To sustainably deliver free basic internet services to people, we need to build apps that use data very efficiently.

Operators have made significant economic investments to bring the internet to people globally, and Internet.org needs to be sustainable for operators so that they can continue to invest in the infrastructure to maintain, improve and expand their networks.

Websites that require high-bandwidth will not be included. Services should not use VoIP, video, file transfer, high resolution photos, or high volume of photos.

<strong>3. Technical specifications</strong>

Websites must be built to be optimized for browsing on both feature and smartphones and in limited bandwidth scenarios. In addition, websites must be properly integrated with Internet.org to allow zero rating and therefore can’t require JavaScript or SSL/TLS/HTTPS and must meet our technical guidelines.

—

For more information on how to work with Internet.org, visit internet.org/platform.

—

<strong>Update as of 5/12/15 to Technical Specifications:</strong> Content and services relying on SSL/TLS will only appear within the Internet.org Android App and not on mobile web until we have a solution there as well.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Today, we’re introducing the Internet.org Platform, an open program for developers to easily create services that integrate with Internet.org. We’re also giving people more choice over the free basic services they can use.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>38</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2015-05-04 15:44:38]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2015-05-04 15:44:38]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[announcing-the-internet-org-platform]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_7eadbba6b10254e505abc10e37a9480c]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/126762664" width="640" height="360" frameborder="0" title="Announcing the Internet.org Platform" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_7eadbba6b10254e505abc10e37a9480c]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1439385815]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_c8ffc78e1d712c96d8435d3da9e324c7]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/126762664" width="660" height="371" frameborder="0" title="Announcing the Internet.org Platform" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_c8ffc78e1d712c96d8435d3da9e324c7]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1439396321]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Internet.org App Now Available in India</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2015/02/10/internet-org-app-now-available-in-india/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2015 15:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=13</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-14" src="http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/10935987_1619431301612412_734379887_n.jpg" alt="10935987_1619431301612412_734379887_n" />

Late last year Facebook hosted the first Internet.org Summit in New Delhi, India. The Summit, and keynote from Mark Zuckerberg, addressed barriers to internet connectivity and explored ways to provide internet access to more than a billion people in India who aren't yet connected.

Today, Facebook and Reliance Communications are making the internet available to millions of people in India through the launch of the Internet.org app and free basic services. This is the first time the Internet.org app will be available in the region.

Reliance customers in six Indian states (Tamil Nadu, Mahararashtra, Andhra Pradesh, Gujarat, Kerala, and Telangana) will now have access to more than three dozen services ranging from news, maternal health, travel, local jobs, sports, communication, and local government information.

The full list of free services includes:

<a href="http://aajtak.intoday.in/">Aaj Tak</a> - Read news in Hindi

<a href="http://m.accuweather.com/en/in/india-weather?partner=internetorg">AccuWeather</a> - Get updated weather information

<a href="http://amarujala.com/">amarujala.com</a> - Read news in Hindi

<a href="http://apspeaks-web.herokuapp.com/">AP Speaks</a> - Engage with local government

<a href="http://www.babajob.com/">Babajob</a> - Search for jobs

<a href="http://in.mama.hub.unicore.io/">BabyCenter &amp; MAMA</a> - Learn about pregnancy and children

<a href="http://m.bbc.com/news">BBC News</a> - Read news from around the world

<a href="http://m.bing.com/">Bing Search</a> - Find information

<a href="http://www.cleartrip.com/m/trains%EF%BB%BF">Cleartrip</a> - Check train and flight schedules &amp; buy tickets

<a href="http://mdaily.bhaskar.com/%EF%BB%BF">Daily Bhaskar</a> - Read local news

<a href="http://dictionary.com/">Dictionary.com</a> - Search for meanings of words

<a href="http://phone.espncricinfo.com/">ESPN Cricinfo</a> - Get cricket updates

<a href="http://m.facebook.com/">Facebook</a> - Communicate with friends and family

<a href="http://in.ffl.hub.unicore.io/">Facts for Life</a> - Find health and hygiene information

<a href="http://in.gem.hub.unicore.io/?language=eng_UK%EF%BB%BF">Girl Effect</a> - Read articles and tips for girls

<a href="http://202.87.41.147/play/free/">HungamaPlay</a> - Listen to music

<a href="http://m.ibnlive.in.com/">IBNLive</a> - Read news

<a href="http://www.empowerwomen.org/ilearn">iLearn</a> - Learn from Women Entrepreneurs

<a href="http://m.indiatoday.in/">India Today</a> - Read local news

<a href="http://220.226.104.36/internetbasics/CS?pageId=0">Internet Basics</a> - Learn about the basics of the Internet

<a href="http://m.jagran.com/english">Jagran</a> - Read local news

<a href="http://m.jagranjosh.com/">Jagran Josh</a> - Get education and career information

<a href="http://m.maalaimalar.com/ArticleListing.aspx?Id=1&amp;Main=18">Maalai Malar</a> - Read news in Tamil

<a href="http://www.mtmobile.in/regular/">Maharashtra Times</a> - Read news in Marathi

<a href="http://in.mnm.hub.unicore.io/">Malaria No More</a> - Learn about malaria

<a href="http://manoramanews.com/">manoramanews.com</a> - Read local news

<a href="https://www.messenger.com/">Messenger</a> - Send messages to friends and family

<a href="http://www.ndtv.com/us?site=full">NDTV</a> - Read news

<a href="http://m.newshunt.com/india/english-newspapers/c-in-l-english%EF%BB%BF">Newshunt</a> - Read news in English

<a href="http://olx.in/?language=en-IN">OLX</a> - Buy and sell products and services

<a href="http://bit.ly/1BWVJyW%EF%BB%BF">Reliance Astrology</a> - Read your horoscope

<a href="http://app.rmlglobal.com/wap/user/demo/dashboard">Reuters Market Lite</a> - Get farming and crop information

<a href="http://blood.is/">Socialblood</a> - Register to donate blood

<a href="http://m.timesofindia.com/">Times of India</a> - Read news

<a href="http://m.timesjobs.com/mobile/promoteTJApps.html?downloadCookie=no%EF%BB%BF">TimesJobs</a> - Search for jobs

<a href="http://translate.reference.com/translate?src=en&amp;dst=hi%EF%BB%BF">Translator</a> - Translate words and phrases

<a href="http://en.m.wikipedia.org/">Wikipedia</a> - Find information

<a href="http://m.wikihow.com/Main-Page%EF%BB%BF">wikiHow</a> - Find information

Reliance customers in India can access these services in the Internet.org Android app, at <a href="https://internet.org/">www.internet.org</a>, from the start screen of the <a href="http://www.opera.com/mobile/mini">Opera Mini</a> mobile web browser, and using the Android app UC Browser for Internet.org. Most of the services will be available in English, Hindi, Tamil, Telugu, Malayalam, Gujarati and Marathi.

This is a big step forward in our efforts to connect everyone to the internet, and to help people share their ideas and creativity with the entire world. We’ll continue to improve the experience and roll it out to other parts of the world.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Today, Facebook and Reliance Communications are making the internet available to millions of people in India through the launch of the Internet.org app and free basic services.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>39</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2015-02-10 15:49:25]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2015-02-10 15:49:25]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[internet-org-app-now-available-in-india]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_excerpt_image]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Internet.org App Available in Ghana</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2015/01/22/internet-org-app-available-in-ghana/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 12:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=16</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Following the launch of the Internet.org app in Zambia and Kenya, Facebook is expanding its partnership with Airtel to bring the app to Ghana.

As part of the Internet.org app, Airtel customers in Ghana will now have access to a set of websites and services for free, in categories including maternal health, education, news and sports updates, and local information.

<img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-17" src="http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/10574705_1550472085202316_1241347262_n.png" alt="10574705_1550472085202316_1241347262_n" />

The full list of free services includes:

<a href="http://m.accuweather.com/en/gh/ghana-weather?partner=internetorg">AccuWeather</a> - Get updated weather information

<a href="http://gh.mama.hub.unicore.io/">BabyCenter &amp; MAMA</a> - Learn about pregnancy and children

<a href="http://www.bbc.com/news/">BBC News</a> - Read news from around the world

<a href="http://gh.ebola.hub.unicore.io/locale/?language=eng_UK">Ebola Information</a> - Get information about Ebola from UNICEF

<a href="http://m.facebook.com/">Facebook</a> - Communicate with friends and family

<a href="http://gh.ffl.hub.unicore.io/">Facts for Life</a> - Find health and hygiene information from UNICEF

<a href="http://live.fundza.mobi/">FunDza</a> - Read books &amp; stories

<a href="http://mobile.ghanaweb.com/wap.classic/">GhanaWeb</a> - Get news and information about Ghana

<a href="http://gh.gem.hub.unicore.io/">Girl Effect</a> - Read articles and tips for girls

<a href="http://mobile.jobberman.com.gh/">Jobberman</a> - Search for jobs

<a href="https://www.facebook.com/mobile/messenger">Messenger</a> - Send messages to friends and family

<a href="http://ghana.news24.com/">News24</a> - Ghana news

<a href="http://www.scholars4dev.com/international-scholarships-for-ghanaian-students/">Scholars4Dev</a> - Find scholarships abroad

<a href="http://gh.supersport.mobi/">SuperSport</a> - Get sports updates

<a href="http://tonaton.com/">Tonaton.com</a> - Buy and sell products

<a href="http://m.wattpad.com/?l=1&amp;q=classics">Wattpad</a> - Read books &amp; stories

<a href="http://en.m.wikipedia.org/">Wikipedia</a> - Find information

Ghana is the fifth country we’ve connected with Internet.org, after Zambia, Tanzania, Kenya and Colombia. More people can now use the internet for free to find jobs, read books, and stay connected and we hope to bring the Internet.org app to more countries soon.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Following the launch of the Internet.org app in Zambia and Kenya, Facebook is expanding its partnership with Airtel to bring the app to Ghana]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>40</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2015-01-22 12:35:31]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2015-01-22 12:35:31]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[internet-org-app-available-in-ghana]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_excerpt_image]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Internet.org App Launches in Colombia</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2015/01/14/internet-org-app-launches-in-colombia/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 12:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=19</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Today, at an event in Bogotá, Colombia, Mark Zuckerberg and President Juan Manuel Santos announced the availability of Facebook‘s Internet.org app for Tigo customers in Colombia.

Through the app, Tigo customers in Colombia will have free access to government services including: Instituto Colombiano para la Evaluación de la Educación, an education assessment service and Agronet, a service that provides information on agriculture and rural development.

<img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-20" src="http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/10935984_766705540081055_409169988_n.png" alt="10935984_766705540081055_409169988_n" />

This is the first time the Internet.org app is available in Latin America, and it’s also the first to include government services as part of the other free basic services in the areas of education, health, communication, jobs, finance, and local information.

The full list of free services includes:

<a href="http://m.1doc3.com/">1doc3</a>

<a href="http://io.24symbols.net/">24 Symbols</a>

<a href="http://m.accuweather.com/es/co/colombia-weather?partner=internetorg">AccuWeather</a>

<a href="http://agronet.gov.co/www/htm3b/noticias2uniNuke_2011_mobile.asp">Agronet</a>

<a href="http://co.mama.hub.unicore.io/">BabyCenter &amp; MAMA</a>

<a href="http://free.facebook.com/">Facebook</a>

<a href="http://co.gem.hub.unicore.io/">Girl Effect</a>

<a href="http://www.icfes.gov.co/">Instituto Colombiano para la Evaluación de la Educación</a>

<a href="https://www.facebook.com/mobile/messenger">Messenger</a>

<a href="http://www.mitula.com.co/">Mitula</a>

<a href="http://co.ffl.hub.unicore.io/">Para la Vida</a>

<a href="http://yourmoneyguide.mobi/co/saving/es">Su Dinero</a>

<a href="http://co.tambero.com/">Tambero.com</a>

<a href="http://unicef.com.co/derechos">UNICEF</a>

<a href="http://www.wikipedia.org/">Wikipedia</a>

<a href="http://www.empowerwomen.org/ilearn?sc_lang=es">YoAprendo</a>

Making the internet accessible through a set of basic services can lead to more people getting online and discovering services they might not have otherwise. We’ll continue to add additional services and bring the app to other parts of the world.

<a href="http://www.millicom.com/media/millicom-news-features/colombia-facebook/">Read more about the update</a>.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Today, at an event in Bogotá, Colombia, Mark Zuckerberg and President Juan Manuel Santos announced the availability of Facebook‘s Internet.org app for Tigo customers in Colombia.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>41</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2015-01-14 12:38:19]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2015-01-14 12:38:19]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[internet-org-app-launches-in-colombia]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_old_slug]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[19]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_excerpt_image]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Internet.org App Comes to Kenya</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2014/11/14/internet-org-app-comes-to-kenya/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 12:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=23</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Starting today the Internet.org app will be available to Airtel subscribers in Kenya.

<img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-24" src="http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/851542_616190575170030_947458292_n.jpg" alt="851542_616190575170030_947458292_n" />

The app, launched to Airtel subscribers in Zambia in July and Tigo subscribers in Tanzania in October, provides people with free access to basic internet services so they can browse useful health, education, finance, employment, communication and local information and services without data charges.

Through the Internet.org app, Airtel customers will have access to:

AccuWeather

BabyCenter &amp; MAMA

BBC News

BBC Swahili

BrighterMonday

Daily Nation

Facebook

Facts for Life

Girl Effect

Jamii Forums

Messenger

OLX

Scholars4Dev

SuperSport

Totohealth

UNICEF Ebola Information

Wattpad

Wikipedia

<a class="aboutApolloCMSPostLink" href="http://africa.airtel.com/wps/wcm/connect/africarevamp/kenya/home/about/media-room/press-releases/internet.org-app">Read more about the update</a>.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Beginning today, the Internet.org app will also be available to Airtel subscribers in Kenya. The app provides access to basic internet services without data charges.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>42</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2014-11-14 12:41:45]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2014-11-14 12:41:45]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[internet-org-app-comes-to-kenya]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_excerpt_image]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Internet.org App Launches in Tanzania</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2014/10/29/internet-org-app-launches-in-tanzania/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=26</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-27" src="http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/10734286_1502269436695826_1165737537_n-201x300.png" alt="10734286_1502269436695826_1165737537_n" />



Starting today the Internet.org app will be available to Tigo subscribers in Tanzania.



The app, launched to Airtel subscribers in Zambia in July, provides people with free access to basic internet services so they can browse useful health, education, finance, employment, communication and local information and services without data charges.



Through the Internet.org app, Tigo customers will have access to:



AccuWeather

BabyCenter &amp; MAMA

BBC News &amp; BBC Swahili

BrighterMonday

The Citizen

Facebook

Facts for Life

Girl Effect

Messenger

Mwananchi

Mwanaspoti

OLX

Shule Direct

SuperSport

Tanzania Today

Wikipedia



We’ll continue to improve the experience and roll it out to other parts of the world. <a href="http://www.tigo.co.tz/tigo-world/press-room/corporate/tigo-offers-free-access-basic-internet-services-through-facebook">Read more about the update</a>.



<em>Updated as of 12/15/14:</em> We’ve added three additional services to the Internet.org app in Tanzania:



Jamii Forums

UNICEF Ebola Information

ZoomTanzania]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Today we’re providing people in Tanzania with free access to basic internet services so they can browse useful health, education, finance, employment, communication and local information online.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>43</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2014-10-29 12:45:00]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2014-10-29 12:45:00]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[internet-org-app-launches-in-tanzania]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_excerpt_image]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Improving App and Network Performance in Indonesia</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2014/10/12/improving-app-and-network-performance-in-indonesia/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2014 12:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=29</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[More than 85% of the world’s population lives in areas with existing cellular coverage, yet only about 30% of the total population accesses the internet. So for most people, the barrier to connectivity isn’t a signal, it’s the ability to afford data. Developers can play a key role in bringing down the cost of the internet by building more data efficient apps for communities where data is less accessible.



To help address this, Facebook hosted an Internet.org developer workshop with Ericsson and XL Axiata, in Jakarta, Indonesia. At the event, developers worked alongside engineers from Facebook, Ericsson and XL to optimize the performance of their apps and make them more efficient. Developers also had the opportunity to test their apps and measure user experience under local network conditions. Earlier this year, Facebook launched a series of <a href="https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?v=556330137796379">hackathons</a>with Ericsson focused on improving data efficiency, which led to the creation of the <a href="https://internet.org/innovationlab">Internet.org Innovation Lab</a>, a space that will give developers the ability to test their apps in real world environments at Facebook’s headquarters.



In addition to building apps that use less data, we need more efficient infrastructure to serve people in low bandwidth areas. This means improving network performance so more people can benefit from being connected. Over the last year, Facebook worked with Ericsson and XL Axiata in Indonesia to create a methodology to analyze, monitor and improve end-to-end network performance using simulated Facebook application use cases. Through this process, the group identified user-impacting issues and addressed them throughout the network. The network-wide adjustments delivered up to 70 percent improvement in network performance from the user perspective. We now know that it is possible to increase network performance using existing network resources, which is key to helping close the connectivity gap. You can learn more about the project in an Internet.org white paper released today titled, “Measuring and improving network performance – an analysis of network and application research, testing and optimization.”



Part of Internet.org’s mission is to work across the industry to cultivate and share learnings. Thanks to this research, we now have a replicable model for analyzing, measuring and improving network performance that can be applied to any mobile network. This will help operators cost-effectively target network improvements to the areas that affect users most, which means greater utility for the two thirds of the world not yet connected.



<a href="https://fbcdn-dragon-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xap1/t39.2365-6/10734295_270843076447514_1952370192_n.pdf" target="_blank">Read the full white paper</a>.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Delivering on Internet.org’s mission will require us to focus on data and network efficiency.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>44</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2014-10-12 12:48:02]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2014-10-12 12:48:02]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[improving-app-and-network-performance-in-indonesia]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Announcing the Internet.org Innovation Challenge in India</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2014/10/09/announcing-the-internet-org-innovation-challenge-in-india/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 13:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=31</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[A recent report by McKinsey &amp; Company found that one of the leading barriers to internet adoption is the lack of relevant, local and multilingual content and services online.



Making sure everyone around the world has access to the internet requires companies, governments and individuals to work together to remove connectivity barriers. Fully realizing Internet.org’s vision of a connected world will require giving people access to apps, websites and services that are relevant to their lives and readable in their own languages.



Today we’re announcing the Internet.org Innovation Challenge in India, an effort to recognize those who are working to make the internet more relevant to four populations that are currently underserved in India: women, students, farmers and migrant workers.



These communities face some of the largest structural barriers to going online and the content they find once they are connected is often of little value.



We will be presenting four $250,000 USD Innovation Challenge Award prizes: one to the leading app, website or service or idea that best meets the needs of each of the designated population categories. Two $25,000 USD Impact Award prizes will also be granted in each category.



Winners will be announced at Mobile World Congress in March 2015, and interested individuals, organizations and groups can submit applications through Jan. 31, 2015. <a href="https://internet.org/innovationchallenge">Learn more and apply</a>.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Internet.org announces an effort to recognize those who are working to make the internet more relevant to four populations that are currently underserved in India: women, students, farmers and migrant workers.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>45</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2014-10-09 13:18:41]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2014-10-09 13:18:41]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[announcing-the-internet-org-innovation-challenge-in-india]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aYggcyvkndY]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Offline and Falling Behind</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2014/09/30/offline-and-falling-behind/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 13:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=33</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Bringing the next 4.4 billion people online will require companies, governments and civil society to work together to remove barriers that stand in the way of a more connected world.



A new study released today from McKinsey &amp; Company, “Offline and falling behind: Barriers to internet adoption,” with research conducted in collaboration with Facebook, identifies the barriers that impede consumers from gaining access to the internet. The study examines the trends that have fueled internet growth, the demographics of the offline population and describes four categories of barriers: incentives, low incomes and affordability, user capability, and infrastructure.



The report found that there are currently 4.4 billion people without internet access, and 3.4 billion of those people live within 20 countries. The offline population is disproportionately rural, low income, elderly, illiterate and female. For example, between 1.1 billion and 2.8 billion people are out of range of an existing mobile network; 920 million people offline are illiterate; and, in developing countries, women are 25 percent less likely to be connected than men. An estimated 3.8 billion to 4.2 billion individuals will still lack access to the internet in 2017.



The report also introduces the “Internet Barriers Index,” a detailed study based on the combination and severity of the barriers facing 25 countries. For example, countries such as Egypt, India and Indonesia face the greatest challenges with respect to incentives and infrastructure. In India, internet adoption is showing steady growth, but the current internet penetration rate is only 15 percent. The goal of the Index is to help identify similarities and common challenges, which may help government and industry facilitate the development of solutions.



As part of the effort to address the barriers to internet access, Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg will keynote the first Internet.org Summit in New Delhi, India next week. While in India, Mark will also meet with Prime Minister Narendra Modi to collaborate on ways to accelerate connectivity in India.



<a href="http://www.mckinsey.com/insights/high_tech_telecoms_internet/offline_and_falling_behind_barriers_to_internet_adoption">Read the full report</a>.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[A new report from McKinsey &amp; Company identifies key barriers to connectivity in order to help companies, governments and civil society bring the next 4.4 billion people online.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>46</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2014-09-30 13:21:22]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2014-09-30 13:21:22]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[offline-and-falling-behind]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Introducing the Internet.org App</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2014/07/31/introducing-the-internet-org-app/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 13:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=35</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[By Guy Rosen, Product Management Director



Over 85% of the world’s population lives in areas with existing cellular coverage, yet only about 30% of the total population accesses the internet. Affordability and awareness are significant barriers to internet adoption for many and today we are introducing the Internet.org app to make the internet accessible to more people by providing a set of free basic services.



With this app, people can browse a set of useful health, employment and local information services without data charges. By providing free basic services via the app, we hope to bring more people online and help them discover valuable services they might not have otherwise.



The Internet.org app will be available first to Airtel subscribers in Zambia and we’ll continue to improve the experience and roll it out to other parts of the world.



<img class="alignright size-full wp-image-37" src="http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/10173493_245433065666993_1670836034_n.png" alt="10173493_245433065666993_1670836034_n" />



Through the Internet.org app, Airtel customers in Zambia will have basic access to:



<a href="http://www.accuweather.com/">AccuWeather</a>

<a href="http://www.airtel.com/">Airtel</a>

<a href="http://ezelibrary.bongohive.co.zm/">eZeLibrary</a>

<a href="https://www.facebook.com/">Facebook</a>

<a href="http://www.factsforlifeglobal.org/">Facts for Life</a>

<a href="https://www.google.com/">Google Search</a>

<a href="http://gozambiajobs.com/jobs">Go Zambia Jobs</a>

<a href="http://kokoliko.net/">Kokoliko</a>

<a href="http://www.mobilemamaalliance.org/">MAMA (Mobile Alliance for Maternal Action)</a>

<a href="https://www.facebook.com/mobile/messenger">Messenger</a>

<a href="http://www.wikipedia.org/">Wikipedia</a>

<a href="http://www.zamrize.org/wrapp/">WRAPP (Women’s Rights App)</a>

<a href="http://www.unicef.org/zambia/health_nutrition_12205.html">Zambia uReport</a>



Airtel customers in Zambia can access these services in the Internet.org Android app, at <a href="https://internet.org/">internet.org</a>, or within the Facebook for Android app.



<a href="https://internet.org/press/quotes">Read what people are saying</a> about the Internet.org app.



<i>Updated as of 10/16/14:</i> We’ve added three additional services to the Internet.org app in Zambia:



SuperSport

Zambia Reports

Ebola FAQ by UNICEF



<i>Updated as of 11/11/14:</i> Zambians are using the Internet.org app to access information and connect with each other. Meet a few of them in this 5-minute <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zS6xBV4ZwZY">video</a>.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[The Internet.org app, initially available in Zambia, gives people free access to a set of basic internet services, including useful health, employment and location information websites.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>47</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2014-07-31 13:23:49]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2014-07-31 13:23:49]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[introducing-the-internet-org-app]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_thumbnail_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[88]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_excerpt_image]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Connecting the World from the Sky</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2014/03/28/connecting-the-world-from-the-sky/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 14:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=39</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Connecting the world is one of the fundamental challenges of our time. To connect everyone in the world, we need to invent new technologies that can solve some of the physical barriers to connectivity. That’s why Facebook is investing in building technologies to deliver new types of connectivity on the ground, in the air and in space.



Yesterday Facebook announced details of how its Connectivity Lab is working to connect the world from the sky with drones, satellites and lasers.



Today, we’re sharing some thoughts from Mark Zuckerberg, Facebook founder and CEO, on the Connectivity Lab’s approach here and progress achieved with Internet.org to date.



These are rough thoughts and are not meant to be a formal technical paper, but offer more detail for those who are interested.



<a href="https://fbcdn-dragon-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-ash3/t39.2365-6/851574_611544752265540_1262758947_n.pdf" target="_blank">Continue reading…</a>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg discusses how different communities require different solutions for connectivity, and what the Connectivity Lab at Facebook is doing to make internet access available throughout the world.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>48</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2014-03-28 14:08:50]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2014-03-28 14:08:50]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[connecting-the-world-from-the-sky]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Announcing the Connectivity Lab at Facebook</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2014/03/27/announcing-the-connectivity-lab-at-facebook/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 14:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=41</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img class="size-full wp-image-42 alignnone" src="http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/851567_645466882191920_2086759051_n.jpg" alt="851567_645466882191920_2086759051_n" />

Last year Facebook and other tech companies launched Internet.org, a global partnership to make the internet available to the two thirds of the world’s population that doesn’t have it. We believe connecting the world is one of the greatest challenges of our generation, and that everyone deserves access to the knowledge, tools and opportunities that come from being connected.

Today, Mark Zuckerberg <a href="https://www.facebook.com/zuck/posts/10101322049893211">announced</a> a team at Facebook that has been working on new technologies to improve and extend internet access. Begun by the same engineering talent behind Facebook’s infrastructure team and the Open Compute Project, the Connectivity Lab team has been working on developing new platforms for connectivity on the ground, in the air and in orbit.

To make these platforms a reality we’ve recently added some of the world’s top experts on aerospace technology including the team from Ascenta, a UK-based company with a deep expertise in designing and building high-altitude long-endurance (HALE) aircraft. The five-member Ascenta team has combined more than 100 years of experience in the aerospace industry including leadership positions with QinetiQ, Boeing, Honeywell and the Harris Corporation. They have worked on noteworthy projects like the Breitling Orbiter and early versions of Zephyr, which became the world's longest flying solar-powered unmanned aircraft.

Other recent additions to the team have come from organizations including NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory, NASA’s Ames Research Center, and the National Optical Astronomy Observatory.

The team’s approach is based on the principle that different sized communities need different solutions and they are already working on new delivery platforms—including planes and satellites—to provide connectivity for communities with different population densities.

For suburban areas in limited geographical regions, we’ve been working on solar-powered high altitude, long endurance aircraft that can stay aloft for months, be quickly deployed and deliver reliable internet connections.

For lower density areas, low-Earth orbit and geosynchronous satellites can beam internet access to the ground.

For all of these systems, the team is looking at Free-space optical communication, or FSO, is a way of using light to transmit data through space using invisible, infrared laser beams. FSO is a promising technology that potentially allows us to dramatically boost the speed of internet connections provided by satellites and drones.

More info on our approach can be found <a href="https://www.facebook.com/l.php?u=https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FpxX6r-xDgG4&amp;h=JAQF23tFp&amp;s=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">here</a>.

Facebook is focused on solving hard engineering problems by building ambitious solutions to address them. We’re looking to people who share this passion and we’ve posted open positions for this team on the <a href="https://www.facebook.com/careers/teams/infrastructure">Facebook Careers page</a>.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg announces a team at Facebook that has been working on new technologies to improve and extend internet access. The Connectivity Lab team is developing platforms for connectivity on the ground, in the air and in orbit.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>49</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2014-03-27 14:10:57]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2014-03-27 14:10:57]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[announcing-the-connectivity-lab-at-facebook]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_thumbnail_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[56]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_excerpt_image]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Highlights from Mark Zuckerberg’s keynote at Mobile World Congress</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2014/02/25/highlights-from-mark-zuckerbergs-keynote-at-mobile-world-congress/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 14:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=44</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[On Monday, at the GSMA’s Mobile World Congress in Barcelona, Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg kicked off the event with a fireside chat with author and journalist David Kirkpatrick. Mark spoke about <a href="https://www.facebook.com/l.php?u=https%3A%2F%2Finternet.org%2F&amp;h=cAQFiRpvE&amp;s=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Internet.org</a> and the importance of making internet access available to the two-thirds of the world not yet connected.



Below are a few highlights from Mark’s remarks during the discussion:



“Only 2.7 billion people have access to the Internet and it's growing more slowly than you think. The main cost is not the smart phone; it's the cost of the data access. We are really not on a path at this point to connect everyone in the world.”



“[Internet access] is really important, because connectivity is not an end in itself. It's what connectivity can bring. There was this Deloitte study that came out the other day that said if you could connect everyone in emerging markets, you could create more than 100 million jobs and bring a lot of people out of poverty.”



“More than 80% of people in the world live in a place where there is already 2G or 3G service. The reasons you might not have connectivity is cost, but then also the question of why you would want to spend your money. You have never had access to the Internet so you don't even know why you would want it. In the US we have 911 to get basic services. Similarly, we want to create a basic dial tone for the Internet. Basic messaging, basic Web information, basic social networking.”



“In the Philippines, we have seen the number of users of the internet double. We did that with The Globe in that country. We made services such as Facebook free. Once you make it economical to do that, you can add other services such as Wikipedia. We've also worked with Tigo, and they've seen growth of Internet users rise by 50%. The early results are extremely promising.”



“What we want to do next is have a year-long period to dive into this with folks to show that the model works. And then we could come back here in a year or two and have a more programmatic way to work with carriers.”



“We did this hackathon recently with Ericsson where developers could get a feel for what their apps do to the bandwidth requirements. You really come away with empathy for the people you're serving and how bad the experience can be. It's about internalizing that empathy.”



To read more about the new projects mentioned during today’s fireside chat, visit the Facebook <a href="https://www.facebook.com/l.php?u=https%3A%2F%2Fnewsroom.fb.com%2FNews%2F809%2FInternet-org-Updates-at-Mobile-World-Congress&amp;h=VAQFubbOp&amp;s=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">newsroom</a> or Internet.org <a href="https://www.facebook.com/l.php?u=https%3A%2F%2Finternet.org%2Fpress&amp;h=jAQFxXreu&amp;s=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">press page</a>.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[On Monday, at the GSMA’s Mobile World Congress in Barcelona, Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg kicked off the event with a fireside chat with author and journalist David Kirkpatrick. Mark spoke about Internet.org and the importance of making internet access available to the two-thirds of the world not yet connected.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>50</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2014-02-25 14:14:18]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2014-02-25 14:14:18]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[highlights-from-mark-zuckerbergs-keynote-at-mobile-world-congress]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Value of Connectivity</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2014/02/23/value-of-connectivity/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 14:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=46</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[On behalf of Internet.org, Facebook engaged Deloitte to study the impact internet access can have on economic and social conditions in the developing world. Released today, <i>Value of Connectivity</i> includes compelling findings in support of closing the connectivity gap. The report found that by expanding internet access in developing countries to levels seen today in developed economies, we could increase productivity by as much as 25 percent, generating $2.2 trillion in GDP and more than 140 million new jobs, lifting 160 million people out of poverty.

The report also found that increased internet access would deliver critical information on nutrition, hygiene and disease prevention. Once connected, people gain access to basic tools like health information, financial services and education that can help them live fuller, better lives and join the worldwide economy.

Read the full report <a href="https://fbcdn-dragon-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-ash3/t39.2365/851546_1398036020459876_1878998841_n.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>.

<img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-48" src="http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/851590_1399697540291047_1206365629_n.png" alt="851590_1399697540291047_1206365629_n" />

<img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-47" src="http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/851550_588920584525076_531308628_n.png" alt="851550_588920584525076_531308628_n" />]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[By expanding internet access in developing countries to levels seen today in developed economies, a new Deloitte report found that we could increase productivity by as much as 25 percent, generating $2.2 trillion in GDP and more than 140 million new jobs, lifting 160 million people out of poverty.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>51</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2014-02-23 14:15:30]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2014-02-23 14:15:30]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[value-of-connectivity]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_excerpt_image]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Introducing SocialEDU</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2014/02/23/introducing-socialedu/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 12:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=50</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Internet.org today announced SocialEDU, a pilot project that will provide students in Rwanda with free access to a collaborative online education experience. Internet.org members Facebook and Nokia worked with the Government of Rwanda, Airtel and edX on a program to give students access to free, high-quality, localized educational content via low-cost smartphones.



Students in Rwanda will be able to access content via a Facebook integrated edX app, using free data provided by Airtel on smartphones subsidized by Nokia. To bring device prices down further, the Government of Rwanda will support innovative financing mechanisms, such as interest rate subsidies, micro-loan guarantees, trade-in rebates, and targeted use of its Universal Service Fund.



Read more about SocialEDU <a href="https://www.facebook.com/l.php?u=https%3A%2F%2Fnewsroom.fb.com%2FNews%2F808%2FSocialEDU&amp;h=RAQGMsen3&amp;s=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">here</a>.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Internet.org announces SocialEDU, a pilot project that will provide students in Rwanda with free access to a collaborative online education experience.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>52</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2014-02-23 12:19:43]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2014-02-23 12:19:43]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[introducing-socialedu]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Internet.org Innovation Lab</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2014/02/23/internet-org-innovation-lab/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 11:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=52</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Facebook and fellow Internet.org member Ericsson announced the Internet.org Innovation Lab, an Ericsson-Facebook collaboration that will give developers the ability to test their apps in real world environments at Facebook’s Menlo Park headquarters. Born from a recent Facebook/Ericsson-hosted Internet.org efficiency <a href="https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?v=556330137796379">hackathon</a>, the Internet.org Innovation Lab will simulate network conditions typically found in growth markets, giving developers an environment to test and optimize their applications for new customers across different regions.



Read more about the Internet.org Innovation Lab <a href="http://www.ericsson.com/us/thecompany/press/releases/2014/02/1763215" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">here</a>.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Facebook and Ericsson announce the Internet.org Innovation lab, an Ericsson-Facebook collaboration that will give developers the ability to test their apps in real world environments.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>53</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2014-02-23 11:21:29]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2014-02-23 11:21:29]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[internet-org-innovation-lab]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Unilever and Internet.org Partner to Understand Internet Barriers to Access in India</title>
		<link>http://internetorgvip.nerderylabs.com/blog/2014/02/23/unilever-and-internet-org-partner-to-understand-internet-barriers-to-access-in-india/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 10:23:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wordpress]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://fbiorg.nerderylabs.com/?p=54</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Unilever and Internet.org have joined forces to better understand and address the barriers to internet access for millions across rural India.



Together, Unilever and Internet.org will conduct in-depth research to examine the challenges surrounding internet adoption in rural communities and will leverage this research to inform the development of a series of on-the-ground projects.



Read more about our partnership <a href="http://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.unilever.com%2Fmediacentre%2Fpressreleases%2F2014%2Funileverandinternetorgpartneroninternetstudyforcommunitiesacrossindia.aspx&amp;h=jAQFxXreu&amp;s=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">here</a>.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Unilever and Internet.org announce a joint partnership to better understand and address the barriers to internet access for millions across rural India.]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>54</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2014-02-23 10:23:19]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2014-02-23 10:23:19]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[unilever-and-internet-org-partner-to-understand-internet-barriers-to-access-in-india]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[iop_video_url]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
